

### **About Me**

Web and Mobile Application developer diploma completed with honors I possess experience in Web Design and Development, with abilities in designing and developing user interfaces and debugging. Known for exceptional proficiency in problem solving, also in having excellent time management, communication, and customer handling skills.

## **Contact**



(403) 352-0978



m.js.delcourt@gmail.com



mattdelcourt.github.io



Red Deer, Alberta

# **Programming Languages**



Vue - Junior/Intermediate



React - Junior/Intermediate



Html/CSS - Junior/Intermediate



TS JS JS/TS - Junior/Intermediate



🔀 C# - Junior



Python - Junior



Java - Junior



**Php** PHP - Junior

# MATTHEW **DELCOURT**

## **Experience**

## Field Pro Software - Junior Front-End Dev

Calgary, Alberta(Remote) - September 2023 - January 2024 Practicum - July 2023 - Sept 2023

- Update/Create new VUE components using TS/JS along side the DevExpress library.
- Utilized third party JS library ExcelJS to Generate new and update exisiting excel documents.
- Utilized third party JS library pdfmake to Generate new and update exisiting PDF's.

## Cam-Tel Line Locating - Field Project Manager

Red Deer, Alberta

2015 - 2017, 2018 - 2019

- Locate underground utilities using company provided
- Draw a map of located utilities with company specific
- · Assist with any in house technical issues regarding equipment or software when needed.

## Flaman Fitness - Sales Manager

Red Deer, Alberta

2017 - 2018

- Complete weekly employee reviews.
- Complete inventory reports monthly/quarterly/yearly.
- Hiring and training new employees.
- renewing outdated promotional signage.

# **Education & Training**

## CDI Career College

2022 - 2023

**Diploma** Web and Mobile Application Development

### **Safety Tickets**

CSTS - Permanent First Aid - Expires Nov/2024

H2S - Expires Nov/2024

## Skills

- Unity 3D/2D
- Unreal Engine
- Programming Logic and Design
- DevOps
- GitHub